Guide to the Elizabeth Gurley Flynn Papers TAM.118
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX (Addendum): Files Obtained by Rosalyn Baxandall and Helen Camp under the Freedom of Information Act (FOIA)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4480 - 4570 Reel 29 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4571 - 4635 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4636 - 4710 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4711 - 4792 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4793 - 4847 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4848 - 4930 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4931 - 5013 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5014 - 5122 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5123 - 5216 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5217 - 5289 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5290 - 5316 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5317 - 5373 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5374 - 5439 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5440 - 5503 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5504 - 5593 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5594 - 5724 Reel 29 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5725 - 5810 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5811 - 5889 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5890 - 5962 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5963 - 6073 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6074 - 6176A Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6177 - 6295 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6296 - 6410 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6411 - 6528 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6529 - 6903 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6904 - 7010 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7011 - 7191 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7192 - 7419 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7420 - 7674 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7675 - 7753 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7754 - 7824 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7825 - 7970 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7971 - 8097 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8098 - 8223 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8224 - 8330 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8331 - 8430 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8431 - 8614 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8615 - 8738 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8739 - 8861 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8862 - 8955 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8956 - 9055 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9056 - 9166 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9167 - 9258 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9259 - 9381 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9382 - 9485 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9486 - 9529 Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: Communist Party Briefs Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: Subs. Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI: Miscellaneous Documents (Camp Request) Reel 30 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI NY 100 - 1696 (c. 1941 - 1947) Reel 31 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI NY 100 - 1696 (c. 1947 - 1951) Reel 31 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI NY 100 - 1696 (c. 1951 - 1959) Reel 32 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI NY 100 - 1696 (c. 1960 - 1964) Reel 32 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Bureau of Prisons Reel 32 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Central Intelligence Agency Reel 32 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of Justice: No. 146 - 1 - 51 - 349 Reel 32 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of Justice: No. 146 - 1 - 51 - 3337 Reel 32 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of Justice: No. 146 - 1 - 51 - 3337 Additional Pages Reel 32 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of Justice: Miscellaneous Reel 32 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of State: Miscellaneous Documents Reel 33 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of the Army: Miscellaneous Documents (Camp Request) Reel 33 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of the Navy Reel 33 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of the Treasury: U.S. Customs Service Reel 33 Reel 30 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: U.S. Parole Commission Reel 33 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Intercepted Mail Reel 33 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: "Sanitized Documents"; R. Baxandall v. FBI, DOJ, CIA (CA - 82 - 8736) Reel 33 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Flynn: Research Files: Unprocessed (box 1) (Box 13, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20)
  - Flynn: Research Files: Unprocessed (box 2) (Box 14)
- Series X (Addendum 2): Files from the Reference Center for Marxist Studies Library: (Unprocessed; 1 box)
  - Articles, Including Posthumously Published, 1916-1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Articles About Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, 1950s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Autobiographical Sketch, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Birthday Cards, Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Campaign, People's Rights Party, Bronx 24th Congressional District, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party USA History Commission: Conclusion of Transcript of EGF Interview; Biographical Notes, 1962, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: American Institute for Marxist Studes, re Research on Flynn, 1964-1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Dear Sid (1 letter), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Includes Notes from Herbert Aptheker and a Letter to Jim West, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Letters (2) from Burt Nelson; Lonnie Nelson (Daughter Correspondence), 1961, 1989, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Handwritten Newspaper Columns (3): May Day in Detroit; More on Harvard; Poison Pens, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Index Cards Listing Some of Flynn's Published Writings, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - "Inventory of Material Received" [by CPUSA?] Note: much of this material has been separated, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - League for Mutual Aid: Invitation for a Dinner for Flynn, Feb 24th, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Memorial Meeting Invitation (Honoring Flynn and Benjamin Davis; Baltimore, MD), Feb 27, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Poetry by Flynn: Includes Poshumous Readings and Performances, 1997, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of Flynn (Photocopies), 1913-1960, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Talk: Personal Recollections of the Industrial Workers of the World (15 pp., at New York University), Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Typescripts of Flynn's Columns in The Worker, 1963-1964, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)